skinnerinc.com 2018-09-07

# Privacy Policy | Skinner Auctioneers

Skinner, Inc. values the privacy of all users of our website (skinnerinc.com). Accordingly, we have adopted the following privacy policy.

Please read this policy carefully. It tells you, among other things, what information we gather from you, how we may use or disclose that information, and what efforts we take to protect it. Contact us at _[iskinner@skinnerinc.com](https://www.cloudflare.com/email-protection#5c35323a331c2f37353232392e35323f723f3331)_ if you have any questions regarding this policy’s contents or to correct your personal information.

## Types of Information Collected

We ask for and collect a variety of information from and about users of our website.

We use cookies, which are small data files that our website sends to your browser for storage on your computer’s hard drive, to protect confidential data, track activity at our site, and better tailor our services to your needs and interests. You may disable your browser’s capacity to use cookies, but if you do so, you may not be able to make use of certain functions of our website (including leaving or tracking bids).

Additionally, when you register on our site, we ask for and store your and/or your business’ name, address, email address and other identifying contact data.

## Storage and Security of Information

Skinner is in compliance with the Commonwealth of Massachusetts 201 CMR 17.00: M.G.L. c. 93H Standards For The Protection Of Personal Information Of Residents Of  The Commonwealth. In accordance with these standards, Skinner maintains a Written Information Security Plan (WISP).

Skinner uses industry-standard SSL encryption to transmit customer data over the Internet. Customer information is stored on Skinner’s servers, which are maintained and operated by us or by a trusted third party hosting company.

Please remember that you play a valuable part in security as well. Your password to access our site, which is assigned at registration, should never be shared with anyone. Also, after you have finished using our site, you should log off and exit your browser so no unauthorized persons can use our site with your name and account information. Furthermore, if you provide any information to parties who operate websites that are linked to or from our site, different rules may apply to their collection, use or disclosure of your personal information. We encourage you to review these sites’ policies before revealing any sensitive or personal information.

Regardless of the precautions taken by you or by us, “perfect security” does not exist on the Internet. We cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us, and you transmit such information at your own risk.

## Use of Information

We use your personally identifying information to identify you as a user of the site and to contact you regarding services or products that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also associate your personally identifying information with information we collect about your preferences and activities at the site, such as the particular pages you request at the site and purchases or other transactions you effect through the site. We may vary the content you receive in future visits to the site based on your preferences and activities. We may also use data from many users to compile statistics and better fit our service to our customers’ needs.

We may provide your personally identifying information, and information about your activities and preferences, to other companies wishing to contact you about products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. We may also provide these companies with collective profiles of our user groups and their activities and preferences. Such collective profiles may also be disclosed in describing our site and services to prospective partners, advertisers and other third parties, and for other lawful purposes.

Finally, we may disclose information to fulfill certain legal and regulatory requirements or if we believe, in good faith, that such disclosure is legally required or necessary to protect others’ rights or to prevent harm.

In addition, we will not send unsolicited messages to users of our site who indicate that they do not wish to receive such messages. If you do not wish to receive unsolicited email messages from us, please contact us at [  
iskinner@skinnerinc.com](mailto:iskinner@skinnerinc.com?Subject=Inquiry%20from%20Privacy%20Policy%20Page).

## Changes to Privacy Policy

It may be necessary from time to time for us to modify this policy to reflect changes in the way we collect and use information or changes in privacy-related laws, regulations, and industry standards. Accordingly, we reserve the right to change this policy at any time by posting the revised policy on this website. Thus, it is incumbent on users to check this privacy policy frequently. If at any time you wish to be removed from our system as a result of such changes, please e-mail us at [  
iskinner@skinnerinc.com](mailto:iskinner@skinnerinc.com?Subject=Inquiry%20from%20Privacy%20Policy%20Page).
